[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Native American sauce Mole de Cacahuate, or Peanut Mole, traditionally served with?", "correct_answer": "Chicken", "incorrect_answers": ["Beef", "Fish", "Guinea pig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical term is synonym of jaundice, a condition characterized by yellowing of the skin, sclera and mucous membranes?", "correct_answer": "Icterus", "incorrect_answers": ["Ascites", "Anorexia", "Nausea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Freddy Kruegers middle name?", "correct_answer": "Charles", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert", "Johnathan", "William"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following cards in the game Magic: the Gathering is from the Onslaught Block?", "correct_answer": "Visara, the Dreadful", "incorrect_answers": ["Orims Chant", "Hypnotic Specter", "Savra, Queen of the Golgari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which saltwater lake, bordered on the west by Azerbaijan and Russia, is the largest inland body of water in the world?", "correct_answer": "Caspian Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Tanganyika", "Victoria", "Baikal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sonoma Valley in California is famous in the USA for its long-lived and high quality wine industry.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The birth stones associated with March, September and December can all be found in this color.", "correct_answer": "Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Pink", "White"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these men has not been Vivienne Westwoods husband?", "correct_answer": "Sid Vicious", "incorrect_answers": ["Andreas Kronthaler", "Malcolm McLaren", "Derek Westwood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is known as the White Squirrel Capital of the World, since it is home to the largest colony of albino squirrels?", "correct_answer": "Olney, Illinois", "incorrect_answers": ["Marionville, Missouri", "Columbus, Ohio", "Kenton, Tennessee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word Colorado mean?", "correct_answer": "Colored Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Indian Sky", "Rocky Mountains", "Mountain High"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed U.S. President George W. Bush in Oliver Stones 2008 movie W.?", "correct_answer": "Josh Brolin", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Dreyfuss", "Bruce Willis", "Christian Bale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Ren\u00e9-Robert Cavelier, Sieur de La Salle (Yikes!) claimed the territory he named it La Louisiane, which means....", "correct_answer": "Land of Louis or The Lousiana.", "incorrect_answers": ["Land of Lords or Land of the Lords.", "Land of France or Long Live France.", "Land of Life or The Life."]}]